vidimovie.com 2019-12-21

# Privacy Policy | Vidimovie

  * About Us
  * Contact Us
  * Sitemap
  * DMCA
  * Developers
  * Terms
  * Privacy

## Privacy Overview

### This statement was last updated on 18 April 2016.

Vidimovie.com ("Vidimovie", "We", "Us") is committed to protecting the privacy of all personal information obtained from you during your visits to vidimovie.com ("the Website", "this Website"). This privacy policy explains what personal information we may collect from you and the purposes for which it will be used. By using this website you give your agreement to the data practices described in this policy.

### What information do we collect and how do we use it?

Depending on which website facilities you use, we collect five different types of information. The types of information and uses are explained below.

If you supply your email address to us we may contact you to ask whether you would like to be added to our mailing list, so that we can tell you about our services.

If you are a registered user, we may use information we collect to offer personalized information when you use the website, notify you of changes to our service, ask your opinions and to help us improve our service to you.

## Information Collection

### 1\. Information that you provide to us

We collect and process information that you provide for specific purposes. This may include demographic information such as your name and email address(es). We use the information to provide you with the specific information, product or services that you request from us and to communicate with you. If you contact us we may keep a record of that correspondence.

You may be asked to provide information about yourself when you use certain site facilities such as the contact us and feedback features.

### 2\. Website usage information

We receive and store certain information whenever you interact with us. We collect website usage information from a number of sources:

  * Our web server.
  * URLs passed to us when you navigate to our site.
  * "Tags" placed in web pages that send information to us or our processors.
  * A selection of Internet service providers to measure regional demographics, but are not traceable back to you.
  * A selection of search engine companies.
  * IP addresses.

We collect web usage information during your visits to our site including information on the date, time, page viewed or searched for, tools used, subscriptions and referrals made and other information relating to your browsing activity on our website. We may also use web usage information to create statistical data regarding the use of our website. We will never use or disclose that statistical data to others.

We collect web usage information to help us:

  * Assess the effectiveness of marketing campaigns.
  * Develop and deliver services and information that better meet your needs.
  * Inform you of events, services and products which we believe to be relevant to you.

### 3\. IP Addresses

We monitor and record IP addresses to analyze trends, track users' movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. We also log IP addresses so we are able to block future access to our services if user or server activity violates our terms and conditions, or attempts to disrupt our services.

### 4\. Cookies

Vidimovie has recently updated its privacy policy in compliance with EU Cookie legislation. Please read this to review the updates about which cookies we use and what information we collect on our site. By continuing to use this site, you are agreeing to our updated privacy policy.

When we design websites, our aim is to make them useful, reliable, and easy to use. Sometimes the best way to achieve this involves placing small amounts of information on your device in the form of a text file called a cookie. Cookies cannot be used to identify you personally.

### 5\. Javascript

We use JavaScript, a simple web scripting language, for interaction with users. We also employ it to collect web usage information for the purposes described above.

## Disclosure of Information

We may have to disclose information to government bodies and law enforcement agencies if required to do so by law. We may also disclose information provided by you to other third parties where this is necessary for the purposes set out in this privacy policy. We will only disclose information about you to others where the law allows. We will not sell, rent or disclose your information to any third parties other than those set out in this privacy policy without your consent. We do not transfer your personal information outside of the European Economic Area.

## External Links

This website contains links to many other commercial and non-commercial websites. Anonymous visit or session information may be passed to other websites for the web usage information and user tracking purposes described above. None of this information can be related to an individual user of the website. The operators of other sites may collect information from you which will be used by them in accordance with their own data protection policy.

This privacy policy applies only to our website. We are not responsible for the privacy practices within any other websites. You should always be aware of this when you leave this website and we encourage you to read the privacy statement on any other website that you visit.

## Security

We use leading technologies and security measures to safeguard your information and keep strict security standards to prevent any unauthorized access to it. We use industry-standard encryption software when processing sensitive information and storing names and email addresses in our databases.

## Changes to this policy

This privacy policy may change from time to time as we develop the range of services on the website. When this privacy policy changes, we will place an updated version on this page and where appropriate we will give you the opportunity to review the revised privacy policy and ask you to agree to it. Regularly reviewing this page ensures that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances, if any, we will share it with other parties. You should continue to check the privacy policy before using this site, even if you have visited it in the past. This ensures that you will be aware of any changes.

## Your rights

If your use of this site falls under the Data Protection Act as a personal user, you have a right to request a copy of any information held about you. If you wish to do this, please contact us, explaining that your interest is to review your personal information. We will ensure that your data is gathered and/or purged from the servers we control. We will also need to receive appropriate identification that proves you are the correct person to request the information.

## Our Cookies

When you first access the Website we set a session ID cookie on your device. The purpose of this cookie is to remember the key pieces of information about you and your interactions with the Website. This cookie is used to record and store any searches you make and a list of the videos you watch and movie pages you visit.

This information is stored securely and is not shared with any other party.

The cookie can be manually removed at any time and is set to automatically expire after three days. It can also be disabled by instructing your web browser to refuse cookies from the domain "vidimovie.com".

## Third Party Cookies

### Google Analytics

This site utilises Google Analytics, a popular web traffic analysis package provided by Google Inc. ("Google"). Google utilizes the Data collected to track and examine the use of this Application, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services. Google may use the Data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.

Google Analytics does not collect any personal information about website users. Read the [Google Analytics privacy](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245) document for more details.

For complete information on the cookie Google Analytics sets and which information it collects, please refer directly to the [cookie usage](https://developers.google.com/analytics/devguides/collection/analyticsjs/cookie-usage) section on the Google Developers website.

### CloudFlare

CloudFlare is a traffic optimization and distribution service provided by CloudFlare Inc. The way CloudFlare is integrated means that it filters all the traffic through this Application, i.e. communication between this Application and the User's browser, while also allowing analytical data from this Application to be collected.

We use Cloudflare for our DNS and they set the __cfduid cookie which is used to override any security restrictions based on the IP address the visitor is coming from. For example, if the visitor is in a coffee shop where there are a bunch of infected machines, but the visitor's machine is known trusted, then the cookie can override the security setting. It does not correspond to any user id in the web application, nor does the cookie store any personally identifiable information.

This cookie is strictly necessary for site security operations and cannot be turned off.

Full details can be found in the CloudFlare [security policy](https://www.cloudflare.com/security-policy) article.
